[
{"question": "What does I mean in roman numerals?", "answer": 1},
{"question": "What does II mean in roman numerals?", "answer": 2},
{"question": "What does III mean in roman numerals?", "answer": 3},
{"question": "What does IV mean in roman numerals?", "answer": 4},
{"question": "What does V mean in roman numerals?", "answer": 5},
{"question": "What does VI mean in roman numerals?", "answer": 6},
{"question": "What does VII mean in roman numerals?", "answer": 7},
{"question": "What does VIII mean in roman numerals?", "answer": 8},
{"question": "What does IX mean in roman numerals?", "answer": 9},
{"question": "What does XI mean in roman numerals?", "answer": 11},
{"question": "What does XII mean in roman numerals?", "answer": 12},
{"question": "What does XIII mean in roman numerals?", "answer": 13},
{"question": "What does IXX mean in roman numerals?", "answer": 19},
{"question": "What does XX mean in roman numerals?", "answer": 20},
{"question": "What does M mean in roman numerals?", "answer": 1000},
{"question": "What does IM mean in roman numerals?", "answer": 999},
{"question": "What does MI mean in roman numerals?", "answer": 1001},
{"question": "What does L mean in roman numerals?", "answer": 50},
{"question": "What does C mean in roman numerals?", "answer": 100},
{"question": "What does D mean in roman numerals?", "answer": 500}
]